Secrets kill.
All the Old Knives is a thriller, mystery film directed by Janus Metz.
When the CIA discovers one of its agents leaked information that cost more than 100 people their lives, veteran
operative Henry Pelham is assigned to root out the mole with his former lover and colleague Celia Harrison.
Henry Pelham, played by Chris Pine.
Celia Harrison, played by Thandiwe Newton.
Bill Compton, played by Jonathan Pryce.
Vick Wallinger, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Karl Stein, played by Corey Johnson.
Ernst Pul, played by Jonjo O'Neill.
All the Old Knives is a 2022 American spy thriller film directed by Janus Metz
Pedersen and written by Olen Steinhauer, based on Steinhauer's 2015 novel.
The film stars Chris Pine, Thandiwe Newton, Laurence
Fishburne, Jonathan Pryce and David Dawson.
The film was released by Amazon Studios in limited theaters across the
United States, and on Amazon Prime Video, on April 8, 2022.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia),
based on novel or book, espionage, spy, conspiracy.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.